{
    "quiz": [
        {
            "collectVerbs": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "collectVerbs",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "showAnswers": "False",
                    "subTitle": "Verbs: (Find)",
                    "inputText": "Choose the first verb",
                    "secondAnswers": "true"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Now the queen lay awake all night, thinking of all the odd names that she had ever heard;",
                        "answer": "lay",
                        "secondAnswer": "queen"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'What will you give me to spin gold for you this third time?'",
                        "answer": "will",
                        "secondAnswer": "you"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Then she knew not what to do, and sat down once more to weep;",
                        "answer": "knew",
                        "secondAnswer": "she"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "And round about the wheel went merrily; the work was quickly done, and the straw was all spun into gold.",
                        "answer": "went",
                        "secondAnswer": "wheel"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The second day she began with all the comical names she could hear of, BANDY-LEGS, HUNCHBACK, CROOK-SHANKS,",
                        "answer": "began",
                        "secondAnswer": "she"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": ",but the little gentleman still said to every one of them, 'Madam, that is not my name.'",
                        "answer": "said",
                        "secondAnswer": "gentleman"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The miller's house was close by, and the miller, you must know, had a very beautiful daughter.",
                        "answer": "was",
                        "secondAnswer": "house"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'Good morrow to you, my good lass; what are you weeping for?'",
                        "answer": "are",
                        "secondAnswer": "you"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'All this must be spun into gold before morning, as you love your life.'",
                        "answer": "must",
                        "secondAnswer": "this"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Verbs: (Find)"
        },
        {
            "findSubject": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "findSubject",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "inputText": "Type in the first subject",
                    "showAnswers": "False",
                    "subTitle": "Subjects: (Find)"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Alice was beginning to get very tired of sitting by her sister on the bank, and of having nothing to do",
                        "answer": "Alice"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Once or twice she had peeped into the book her sister was reading,",
                        "answer": "she"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": ",but it had no pictures or conversations in it,",
                        "answer": "it"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": ",'and what is the use of a book,' thought Alice 'without pictures or conversation?'",
                        "answer": "the use"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "So she was considering in her own mind (as well as she could, for the hot day made her feel very sleepy and stupid),",
                        "answer": "she"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": ",whether the pleasure of making a daisy-chain would be worth the trouble of getting up and picking the daisies,",
                        "answer": "the pleasure"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": ",when suddenly a White Rabbit with pink eyes ran close by her.",
                        "answer": "Rabbit"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "There was nothing so VERY remarkable in that;(Dummy subject: There/formelt subjekt: There)",
                        "answer": "nothing"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": ",nor did Alice think it so VERY much out of the way to hear the Rabbit say to itself,",
                        "answer": "Alice"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'Oh dear! Oh dear! I shall be late!'",
                        "answer": "I"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "dfdsdsdsdsdsd"
        },
        {
            "vQuizLantern": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "vQuizLantern",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary",
                    "inputText": "Choose the right word",
                    "showAnswers": "True",
                    "subTitle": "Halloween - Jack O'Lantern"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Then indeed Michael began to cry, and even John could speak in gulps only, for they knew Hook's ...",
                        "answer": "reputation"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "It is sometimes a good idea to ... the brakes on a car.",
                        "answer": "apply"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"So, you think you can ... your way out of this one?\"",
                        "answer": "wiggle"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He told me he would like a roommate; but perhaps you would ... a small room alone?\"",
                        "answer": "prefer"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "our three travellers arrived at one of the ... outposts belonging to the fur-traders.",
                        "answer": "solitary"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Wood carvers ... pieces of wood, removing bit by bit until what's left is a sailor with a yellow raincoat or a lone wolf howling at the moon.",
                        "answer": "whittle"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "When you're being ..., you're thinking of other people before yourself.",
                        "answer": "selfless"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Give me ... to come with you,\" said Kaa.",
                        "answer": "permission"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Means crafty, cunning or tricky. \"Oh, he’s a ... deceiver, Mr. Curtis. I’d like to see him foolin’ around me.",
                        "answer": "sly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The third elephant watched the two go away, ..., wheeled round, and took his own path.",
                        "answer": "snorted"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Full of joy he took it to the king and expected that he would ... him the promised reward.",
                        "answer": "grant"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Means \"to feel sorry for something you've done.\" “Girl, you shall bitterly ... that word!” said Curtis, stung to fury.",
                        "answer": "repent"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "When the countryman saw so much money, he said, 'I will agree to your proposal.' So he took the purse, put up his fiddle, and travelled on very pleased with his...",
                        "answer": "bargain"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "you would hear the whole island ... with life. / I am ... with rage.",
                        "answer": "seething"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "vQuizWitchesWizards": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "vQuizWitchesWizards",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary",
                    "inputText": "Choose the right word",
                    "showAnswers": "True",
                    "subTitle": "Witches and Wizards - Witches and Wizards"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "If you enjoy a story about vampires, witches, werewolves, or ghosts, you like reading about the ...",
                        "answer": "supernatural"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She came back about ten o'clock and gave me a sleeping ...",
                        "answer": "potion"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "... is the study of illness and injuries that teaches doctors how to help people.",
                        "answer": "Medicine"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "qualities or ways of bahaving that are natural and common to most people.",
                        "answer": "human nature"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "have a tendency to do or be something.",
                        "answer": "tend"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "... is about being responsible for something that's bad or has gone wrong.",
                        "answer": "Blame"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I guess you can ... Ted to be on time,\" said Ruth.",
                        "answer": "trust"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Other large international companies have also been ... of avoiding tax in the UK.",
                        "answer": "accused"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "a medicine or therapy",
                        "answer": "cure"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"We mustn't be seen returning to the town together too late for it create ...\"",
                        "answer": "suspicion"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "free from sin",
                        "answer": "innocent"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "perceive to be the same",
                        "answer": "recognize"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "If you are considered trustworthy and kind, you have a good ...",
                        "answer": "reputation"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "insertToBe": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "insertToBe",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verb: to be (nutid/datid)",
                    "inputText": "Insert the verb (to be)",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "They ... like no walrus, sea lion, seal, bear, whale, shark, fish, squid, or scallop that Kotick had ever seen before.",
                        "answer": "were"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "This time, they said, they ... really going to have a leader and become the wisest people in the jungle",
                        "answer": "were"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"What of it? I am sleepy, Bagheera, and Shere Khan ... all long tail and loud talk—like Mao, the Peacock.\"",
                        "answer": "is"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"But this ... no time for sleeping. Baloo knows it; I know it; the Pack know it; and even the foolish, foolish deer know\"",
                        "answer": "is"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Meanwhile, Baloo and Bagheera ... furious with rage and grief.",
                        "answer": "were"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The monkeys never fight unless they ... a hundred to one, and few in the jungle care for those odds.",
                        "answer": "are"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Psshaw! The branches are not what they were when I ... young.",
                        "answer": "was"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "When it ... all over Mowgli sneezed, and picked himself up without a word.",
                        "answer": "was"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"What is the use of running away? I ... sure to catch you. Little fool, look at me!\"",
                        "answer": "am"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I ... not ready yet. Wait a little.",
                        "answer": "am"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "toBeParticiple": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "toBeParticiple",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verb: to be (førnutid/førdatid)",
                    "inputText": "Insert the verb to be",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "'He must ... ... a very clever cook,' said Bunyip",
                        "answer": "have been"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"If I had had this then I might ... ... a different man,\"",
                        "answer": "have been"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I ... ... in State's prison.",
                        "answer": "have been"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She wondered how she could ever ... ... so silly.",
                        "answer": "have been"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I don't care whose pig it is, but wherever it came from it ... ... a very good friend to me.",
                        "answer": "has been"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"It's not there now. Ulyth's ... ... put in its place, and mine's vanished. Come and see.\"",
                        "answer": "has been"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She understood only too well why she ... ... so miserable for the last three days.",
                        "answer": "had been"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Mrs. Arnold ... ... ill, and then had gone away to recruit her health,",
                        "answer": "had been"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "No outdoor exercise ... ... possible that day,",
                        "answer": "had been"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Why is the grass wet? ... it ... raining?\"",
                        "answer": "Has been"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "jaybirdVopcabulary": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "jaybirdVopcabulary",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary",
                    "subTitle": "Native americans - Jaybird",
                    "inputText": "Choose the right word",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Colonists who came to America",
                        "answer": "settlers"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "It's potato ... time and children are helping too - as they have done for centuries.",
                        "answer": "harvest"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Why did the American Indians get ... ...?",
                        "answer": "wiped out"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "On Monday, sound trucks cruised the streets urging people to boil drinking water to prevent infectious ...",
                        "answer": "disease"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The game was simple: The fastest ... won the most profits.",
                        "answer": "traders"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Almost all day the battle ... between the two men.",
                        "answer": "raged"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "... he did not live a hundred years later.",
                        "answer": "Pity"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A ... is a situation that's hard to get out of.",
                        "answer": "plight"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "One series showed police vehicles being ... and burned.",
                        "answer": "overturned"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "When preparing for a foreign occupation, the military instructs troops not to ... sacred sites and risk offending the local population.",
                        "answer": "desecrate"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They built warm ... covered with fur pelts of bear skins.",
                        "answer": "wigwams"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "These were erected by Indian tribes of the northwest Pacific coast",
                        "answer": "totem poles"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Her hands and ankles were tied, and she knew what was to be her fate. She was to be left on the rock to ...,",
                        "answer": "perish"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The wisdom of our ...",
                        "answer": "ancestors"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Not only do they live in constant fear; abused wives also believe they are ...",
                        "answer": "powerless"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "toHaveNutidDatid": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "toHaveNutidDatid",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verb: to have (nutid/datid)",
                    "inputText": "Insert the verb to have",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "I ... no gift of words, but I speak the truth.",
                        "answer": "have"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I ... the Pack and I have thee; and Baloo, though he is so lazy, might strike a blow or two for my sake. Why should I be afraid?\"",
                        "answer": "have"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Bah! What ... we to do with this toothless fool?\"",
                        "answer": "have"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Knowing that I ... no right to speak here, I ask your leave.\"",
                        "answer": "have"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"He ... no right,\" whispered Bagheera.",
                        "answer": "has"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"does Shere Khan lead the Pack? What ... a tiger to do with our leadership?\"",
                        "answer": "has"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"The jungle ... many tongues. I know them all.\"",
                        "answer": "has"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "All this will show you how much Mowgli ... to learn by heart, and he grew very tired of repeating the same thing a hundred times;",
                        "answer": "had"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I went away, and the gray apes came down from the trees and ... pity on me. No one else cared.\"",
                        "answer": "had"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "First he ... to wear a cloth round him, which annoyed him horribly;",
                        "answer": "had"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Baloo made one effort to hurry, but ... to sit down panting",
                        "answer": "had"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizIrregularVerbToSwim": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizIrregularVerbToSwim",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verb: to swim",
                    "inputText": "Skriv den rigtige form af verbet",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Yesterday I had been ... when my phone rang",
                        "answer": "swimming"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Tom  ... in the river (Nutid)",
                        "answer": "swims"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "My head is ...",
                        "answer": "swimming"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Yesterday, everything was ... before my eyes.",
                        "answer": "swimming"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He looked at the fish that ... in the river",
                        "answer": "swam"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Let's go for a ...",
                        "answer": "swim"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I had ... 10 miles when I started to get tired.",
                        "answer": "swum"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "On ordinary occasions the boys would have ... alongside cheering;",
                        "answer": "swum"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We ... in the chilly water (Datid)",
                        "answer": "swam"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I have ... at my dad's house every afternoon this week.",
                        "answer": "swum"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I am ... at my mother's house this afternoon.",
                        "answer": "swimming"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I will ... at my sister's house.",
                        "answer": "swim"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I ... at my brother's house in the afternoon.(Nutid)",
                        "answer": "swim"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He likes to ...",
                        "answer": "swim"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He usually never ... alone.",
                        "answer": "swims"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "warriorMaidenVocabularyJumbled": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "warriorMaidenVocabularyJumbled",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary",
                    "subTitle": "Native americans - The Maiden Warrior",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "When you ... something, you consciously select it and accept it as your own.",
                        "answer": "adopt"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "But when the princess awoke on the following morning she was ...  to see, instead of the frog, a handsome prince.",
                        "answer": "astonished"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Now trust me. Tell me what it is, and trust me. I won't ... you.\"",
                        "answer": "betray"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "But as soon as his cubs are old enough to stand on their feet he must bring them to the Pack ..., which is generally held once a month at full moon,",
                        "answer": "Council"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He had fallen twice into a wolf trap in his youth, and once he had been beaten and left for dead; so he knew the manners and ... of men.",
                        "answer": "customs"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I'm tired of this, but I'll ... it till one o'clock.\"",
                        "answer": "endure"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Being respected.",
                        "answer": "Honored"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Shrub or vine.",
                        "answer": "Honeysuckle"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Stealing valuable things from a place.",
                        "answer": "Pillaging"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": ";then she began to lie in bed in the mornings and ... to get up.",
                        "answer": "refused"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "One of them now noticed a gold ring still ... on the little finger of the murdered girl,",
                        "answer": "remaining"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "... had they set foot on the threshold, when Tom called out, 'Don't bring me any more hay!'",
                        "answer": "Scarcely"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Were sweeter words ever ... by a sweeter woman?",
                        "answer": "uttered"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Shells put into string. Used by native americans.",
                        "answer": "Wampums"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I ... how long we've been down here, Tom? We better start back.\"",
                        "answer": "wonder"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizRegularVerbs": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizRegularVerbs",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verbs: (Find Regular)",
                    "inputText": "Skriv det første regelmæssige verbum",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "We laid there all day, and watched the rafts and steamboats spin down the Missouri shore,",
                        "answer": "watched"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "It tasted so good to her—so very good,",
                        "answer": "tasted"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The next day she longed for it three times as much as before.",
                        "answer": "longed"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "At twilight, he clambered down over the wall into the garden of the enchantress,",
                        "answer": "clambered"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "But Sid's fingers slipped and the bowl dropped and broke.",
                        "answer": "slipped"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Mary looked at him in surprise.",
                        "answer": "looked"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He opened the bag and brought out three stockings,",
                        "answer": "opened"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"You could have chopped the cabin down,\" said the other.",
                        "answer": "chopped"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Just a what?\" asked the conductor as the boy hesitated.",
                        "answer": "asked"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They were professional wise men; they belonged to the learned, the cultured, the thoughtful class;",
                        "answer": "belonged"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizVocabularyWitchChild": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizVocabularyWitchChild",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary",
                    "subTitle": "Witches and Wizards - Witch Child",
                    "inputText": "Type the right word",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "There was once a poor widow who lived in a lonely ...",
                        "answer": "cottage"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A tall tower",
                        "answer": "steeple"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The fish they have caught are ... on bamboo and roasted.",
                        "answer": "skewered"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "You can ... yourself with a wig and mustache;",
                        "answer": "disguise"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The door opened, and a droll-looking little man ... in, and said, 'Good morrow to you, my good lass;'",
                        "answer": "hobbled"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "It was of no use to deny what had happened. They ... it all.",
                        "answer": "confessed"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "With ... eyes they watched every movement.",
                        "answer": "gloating"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "... means to keep from having.",
                        "answer": "Deprive"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "If someone has ..., it means they are worthy of respect.",
                        "answer": "dignity"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'Before bringing ...,' said the Possum, 'prove where the Puddin' is.'",
                        "answer": "accusations"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A cause of great suffering.",
                        "answer": "affliction"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The little tailor ... of the king the promised reward;",
                        "answer": "demanded"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He cried and ... for forgiveness,",
                        "answer": "pleaded"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A ... is a type of song with a repetitive, monotonous structure",
                        "answer": "chant"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Jeffrey MacDonald is never going to admit his ...,\" prosecutor John Bruce said.",
                        "answer": "guilt"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizAdjectiveOrAdverb": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizAdjectiveOrAdverb",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Adjective or Adverb",
                    "inputText": "type the adjective or adverb",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "He ran ... (slow/slowly)",
                        "answer": "slowly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She is a ... learner (slow/slowly)",
                        "answer": "slow"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She runs ... (fast)",
                        "answer": "fast"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They performed ... (bad/badly)",
                        "answer": "badly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The flowers in my garden smell ... (sweet/sweetly)",
                        "answer": "sweet"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The old woman next door looked ... (angry/angrily)",
                        "answer": "angry"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He performed job ... (well/good)",
                        "answer": "well"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The patient looks ... today. (well/good)",
                        "answer": "well"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "You look ... in that dress. (well/good)",
                        "answer": "good"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I feel ... about my decision to study abroad. (good/well)",
                        "answer": "good"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The people in the line moved ... quickly. (incredible/incredibly)",
                        "answer": "incredibly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He did his homework ... correctly. (absolute/absolutely)",
                        "answer": "absolutely"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He sings ... (beautiful/beautifully)",
                        "answer": "beautifully"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She's a very ... runner (quick/quickly)",
                        "answer": "quick"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "This meat tastes ... (bad, badly)",
                        "answer": "bad"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She doesn't seem ... today. (happy/happily)",
                        "answer": "happy"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She performed the audition ... yesterday. (bad/badly)",
                        "answer": "badly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The cheetah moved ... across the savannah. (quick/quickly)",
                        "answer": "quickly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I feel ... about my appearance. (well/good)",
                        "answer": "good"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The doctor decided that he was ... enough to participate in the game. (well/good)",
                        "answer": "well"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizAdjectiveOrAdverb2": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizAdjectiveOrAdverb2",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Adjective or Adverb II",
                    "inputText": "Choose the right word",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "He was in a large apartment, ... furnished.",
                        "answer": "beautifully"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She had a ... room in which she slept alone.",
                        "answer": "beautiful"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "So they came back and whispered ... to him,",
                        "answer": "softly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He turned himself ... about, to get a view of the country.",
                        "answer": "slowly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He just rubbed his face with his large, ... hands.",
                        "answer": "soft"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Some are already available in Europe but approval in the United States has been very ...",
                        "answer": "slow"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Walk ... now till you get away from the houses,",
                        "answer": "fast"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "It was a ... relief for us when the door opened and Doctor Livesey came in, on his visit to my father.",
                        "answer": "happy"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": ";and there they lived ... a great many years.",
                        "answer": "happily"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Then he was very ... and sulky, and would not speak to her at all;",
                        "answer": "angry"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The old woman was as good as her word: she never spoke ... to her, and gave her roast and boiled meats every day.",
                        "answer": "angrily"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'I am pleased that you should want to go back to your own people, and as you have served me so ... and faithfully, I will take you home myself.'",
                        "answer": "well"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'Get up, lazy thing, fetch some water, and cook something ... for your brother,",
                        "answer": "good"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Golden sunlight; Heavenly sky; ... fresh air; merry bells. Oh, glorious! Glorious!",
                        "answer": "sweet"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Looking up so ..., the little girl said, \"Am I dying, auntie?\"",
                        "answer": "sweetly"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizDo": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizDo",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verb: to do (nutid/datid)",
                    "inputText": "Insert the verb to do",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "The dwarfs talked a little while together, and then one said, \"... you think you could be our little housekeeper?",
                        "answer": "Do"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Dear brother, ... not drink,\" she began; but she was too late, for her brother had already knelt by the stream to drink.",
                        "answer": "do"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"What shall we ... now?\" said the boy.",
                        "answer": "do"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The good creature ... as the children wished; she carried Grethel over first, and then came back for Hansel",
                        "answer": "did"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "But Hansel ... not look back any more; he only dropped pieces of bread behind him, as they walked through the wood.",
                        "answer": "did"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They walked all the night through, and ... not reach their father's house till break of day.",
                        "answer": "did"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They had gone but a very short distance when Hansel looked back at the house, and this he ... again and again.",
                        "answer": "did"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She can't help being dumb, but why ... she never laugh?",
                        "answer": "does"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"... she live far off?\" said the wolf. \"Oh yes!\" answered Little Red Riding Hood;",
                        "answer": "Does"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I am so ugly that even the dog ... not like to bite me!\"",
                        "answer": "does"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"To whom ... this beautiful tree belong?\"",
                        "answer": "does"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "At last he said, \"Who are you, and what ... you want?\"",
                        "answer": "do"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "For what indeed could a prince ... with a princess that had lost her gravity?",
                        "answer": "do"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The two eldest replied that they ... not know how to work.",
                        "answer": "did"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"the cottage is good enough for us; what should we ... with a castle?\"",
                        "answer": "do"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizTrickyPrepositions": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizTrickyPrepositions",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Prepositions - tricky.",
                    "inputText": "type the right preposition.",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "I have placed the glass ... the table.(on, at, above)",
                        "answer": "on"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I am ... work today.(on, at, in)",
                        "answer": "at"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We could meet ...  the post office.(at, in, on)",
                        "answer": "at"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She looked directly ... him. (on, at, towards)",
                        "answer": "at"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "It is quiet ... the country.(in, on, at)",
                        "answer": "in"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She climbed ... bed.(to, in, into)",
                        "answer": "into"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "See you ... Christmas!(at, to, by)",
                        "answer": "at"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I go ... school.(in, to, at)",
                        "answer": "to"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I am sitting ... the bus(in, on, at)",
                        "answer": "on"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We were waiting ... the train to arrive.(on, for)",
                        "answer": "for"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Are you interested ... working for us?",
                        "answer": "in"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Sara must be fed up ... studying",
                        "answer": "with"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "What prevented you ... coming to see us?",
                        "answer": "from"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizPrepositionsWithVerb": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizPrepositionsWithVerb",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Prepositions and verbs",
                    "inputText": "Type the preposition and verb",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "We wanted ... ... the building. (leave)",
                        "answer": "to leave"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We weren't allowed ... ... the building. (leave)",
                        "answer": "to leave"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We were prevented ... ... the building. (leave)",
                        "answer": "from leaving"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Sam failed ... ... the problem. (solve)",
                        "answer": "to solve"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jack succeeded ... ... the problem. (solve)",
                        "answer": "in solving"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She's thinking ... ... away next week. (go)",
                        "answer": "about going"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She's hoping ... ... away next month. (go)",
                        "answer": "to go"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They would like ... ... away next year. (go)",
                        "answer": "to go"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I'm looking forward ... ... away next week. (go)",
                        "answer": "to going"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Sara wanted ... ... me lunch. (buy)",
                        "answer": "to buy"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Sara promised ... ... me lunch. (buy)",
                        "answer": "to buy"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Sara insisted ... ... me lunch. (buy)",
                        "answer": "on buying"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Sara wouldn't dream ... ... me lunch. (buy)",
                        "answer": "of buying"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizBoesenHawaiiVocab": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizBoesenHawaiiVocab",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary",
                    "subTitle": "Hawaii - Dear Ms. Boesen",
                    "inputText": "Choose the right word",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "The island of ... is the second-largest of the Hawaiian Islands.",
                        "answer": "Maui"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "... is a place on the north shore of the island of Maui in the U.S. state of Hawaii. It has lent its name to a big wave surfing break, also known as Jaws.",
                        "answer": "Peahi"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Check out this volcanic eruption that's so ... it's been described as looking like the end of the world!",
                        "answer": "spectacular"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A ... is a person who is part mortal and part god.",
                        "answer": "demigod"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "..., or the East Maui Volcano, is a massive shield volcano that forms more than 75% of the Hawaiian Island of Maui.",
                        "answer": "Haleakala"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "... is the capital of Hawaii",
                        "answer": "Honolulu"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "... Beach Park is located on the north shore of Maui, Hawaii, USA. It is a famous windsurfing site on Hawaii.",
                        "answer": "Ho'okipa"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "When you ... something, you show that it's true. “Please ... that the doors are closed”",
                        "answer": "verify"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A ... is a prosthesis that replaces a missing leg.",
                        "answer": "pegleg"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "One day, as he sat on the ... with his rod, looking at the sparkling waves and watching his line, all on a sudden his float was dragged away deep into the water.",
                        "answer": "shore"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Hawaii’s natural scenery, warm tropical climate, public beaches and oceanic surrounding, and active ... make it a popular destination for tourists, surfers, biologists, and volcanologists alike.",
                        "answer": "volcanoes"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He often travels by bus but is also known to walk and ...",
                        "answer": "hitchhike"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A garland of flowers, especially one worn around the neck.",
                        "answer": "lei"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A Hawaiian dance performed by a woman",
                        "answer": "hula"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I am very ... about her economy.",
                        "answer": "concerned"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizVocabHawaiiTodayPeleGoddess": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizVocabHawaiiTodayPeleGoddess",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary",
                    "subTitle": "Hawaii - Hawaii today, Pele the Famous Goddess",
                    "inputText": "Choose the right word",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "..., there are lots of places you can go for advice and guidance.",
                        "answer": "Fortunately"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The ... of the people to give their children a merry Christmas in the popular sense, however, are strong and sometimes pitiful.",
                        "answer": "efforts"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "When people ... they usually say 'I'll see you later'",
                        "answer": "part"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "This verb can be used to describe anything that is released in a quick, violent burst, such as a bomb exploding or lava spewing from a volcano. The volcano is going to ...",
                        "answer": "erupt"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A ... is a safe place.",
                        "answer": "haven"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Something that happens ... doesn't happen all the time, just every once in a while.",
                        "answer": "occasionally"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A ... driver is someone who drives very slowly or avoids highways altogether.",
                        "answer": "timid"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Means with little weight or force",
                        "answer": "gently"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "With all this in our minds, we waded ... as fast as we could, leaving behind us the poor jolly-boat and a good half of all our powder and provisions.",
                        "answer": "ashore"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We've Puddin' here a treat, We've Puddin' here galore; Do not ... to stay and dine, Our Puddin' you'll adore.",
                        "answer": "decline"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He is talented enough to make ... improvements in his game.",
                        "answer": "major"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Unlike oil prices, natural gas prices ... on the international marketplace.",
                        "answer": "vary"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "An elaborate Hawaiian feast or party",
                        "answer": "luaus"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We were very grateful for his ...",
                        "answer": "contributions"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The adjective ... describes someone who is able to attract interest or is easy to like.",
                        "answer": "appealing"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "To make more interesting or flavorful.",
                        "answer": "spice"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The white man",
                        "answer": "Caucasian"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "At first he thought he would wait till daylight. Then his ... got the better of him. \"I won't,\" he said, \"I won't; why should I?\"",
                        "answer": "temper"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Then with a bold and courageous heart, he advanced again, and smote the ... dragon under one of his flaming wings, so that the weapon pierced the heart, and all the grass around turned crimson with the blood that flowed from the dying monster.",
                        "answer": "fiery"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'Laziness—slackness—that's the ... of the modern young man.",
                        "answer": "curse"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "And she was very ... to her; she used to make her do all the servant's work, and never let her have any peace.",
                        "answer": "cruel"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Vile beast!\" cried Giacomo, bringing his fist down with a force which made the house ... as from an earthquake.",
                        "answer": "tremble"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Mary-Ann tried to ... her mother, but the good woman could not and would not listen.",
                        "answer": "calm"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Then the servant said ever so sharp, \"Then move me this Castle and all it contains right away over the sea where the master can't ... us.\"",
                        "answer": "disturb"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I would ... die than eat a pineapple!\"",
                        "answer": "rather"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizToSleepQuiz": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizToSleepQuiz",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verb: to sleep",
                    "inputText": "Indsæt den rigtige form af verbet to sleept",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "I ... all day yesterday. ( Datid )",
                        "answer": "slept"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They ... in the same room. ( Nutid )",
                        "answer": "sleep"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I am sure that you ... ... well tonight. ( Fremtid )",
                        "answer": "will sleep"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Mr. Jones never ... at night. ( Nutid )",
                        "answer": "sleeps"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He ... still ... (Nutid udvidet)",
                        "answer": "is sleeping"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Why ... you not ...? ( Nutid udvidet )",
                        "answer": "are sleeping"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She ... like a log. ( Datid )",
                        "answer": "slept"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They ... ... ... since morning ( Førnutid udvidet )",
                        "answer": "have been sleeping"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "By 12 o'clock tomorrow, I ... ... ... ... for 12 hours. ( Førfremtid udvidet )",
                        "answer": "will have been sleeping"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "quizVerbToSleep": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizVerbToSleep",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verb: to sleep II",
                    "inputText": "Indsæt den rigtige form af verbet to sleep",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Fortunately, he ... ... lightly, and for a like reason.",
                        "answer": "was sleeping"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He awoke once in the night to replenish the fire, but he ... ... soundly at seven o'clock in the morning when the door of the car opened and half a dozen men filed in.",
                        "answer": "was sleeping"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Just before they went to ... the drummer said to me: \"Say, parson, we've got to give those children some Christmas.\"",
                        "answer": "sleep"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We were so excited that we actually could not ....",
                        "answer": "sleep"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I  ... ... much.  I couldn't, somehow, for thinking.  And every time I woke up I thought somebody had me by the neck.",
                        "answer": "didn't sleep"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I often hear it when I ... ...,\" Jane said.",
                        "answer": "am sleeping"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "And when he came into the palace, the flies ... ... on the walls;",
                        "answer": "were sleeping"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "... ... in twelve beds all in one room; and when they went to bed, the doors were shut and locked up;",
                        "answer": "They slept"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "And as for this soldier, even if I had not given him his sleeping draught, he would ... ... soundly enough.'",
                        "answer": "have slept"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "And the princess, though very unwilling, took him up in her hand, and put him upon the pillow of her own bed, where ... ... all night long.",
                        "answer": "he slept"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'You naughty children, why ... you ... so long in the forest?—we thought you were never coming back at all!'",
                        "answer": "have slept"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She went as before to look for him, but ... ..., and it was impossible to awaken him.",
                        "answer": "he slept"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Verb: to sleep II"
        },
        {
            "quizPearlHarborEyeWitnessVocab": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizPearlHarborEyeWitnessVocab",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary",
                    "subTitle": "Hawaii - Pearl Harbor - Eyewitness account. Meaning of words within context.",
                    "inputText": "Type the right word.",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "uneasy",
                        "answer": "ængstelig"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "decision",
                        "answer": "beslutning"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "peninsula",
                        "answer": "halvø"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "jutted",
                        "answer": "stak frem"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "pier",
                        "answer": "anløbsbro"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "rattled",
                        "answer": "klaprede"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "shallow dive",
                        "answer": "dykke lavt"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "altitude",
                        "answer": "højde"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "furiously",
                        "answer": "rasende"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "steeply",
                        "answer": "stejlt"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "fear manifested",
                        "answer": "frygt tilkendegivet"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "responded",
                        "answer": "reagerede"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "manned",
                        "answer": "bemandede"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "exhausting",
                        "answer": "trættende"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "contemplate",
                        "answer": "overveje"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "extended",
                        "answer": "strakte"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "definitely",
                        "answer": "helt sikkert"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "midst",
                        "answer": "midten"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "mind numbing",
                        "answer": "ufatteligt"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "secure",
                        "answer": "sikker"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "word was passed by",
                        "answer": "det forlød sig"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "duty",
                        "answer": "pligt"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "comfort",
                        "answer": "trøst"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "vagualy",
                        "answer": "svagt"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "supplied",
                        "answer": "forsynede"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "obvious",
                        "answer": "åbenlyst"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "considered",
                        "answer": "anset"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "suspicions",
                        "answer": "mistanker"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "pending",
                        "answer": "forestående"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "intermingled",
                        "answer": "blandet"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Pearl Harbor - Eyewitness account. Meaning of words within context"
        },
        {
            "quizPhrasalVerbs": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizPhrasalVerbs",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verbs: Phrasal verbs",
                    "inputText": "Pick the right synonym",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "blow out",
                        "answer": "put out"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "throw away",
                        "answer": "discard"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "look like",
                        "answer": "resemble"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "pass away",
                        "answer": "die"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "pick out",
                        "answer": "choose"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "work out",
                        "answer": "exercise"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "make up",
                        "answer": "create"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "get over",
                        "answer": "recover"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "put off",
                        "answer": "postpone"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "call off",
                        "answer": "cancel"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "hold on",
                        "answer": "wait"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "come across",
                        "answer": "find"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "carry on",
                        "answer": "continue"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "turn on",
                        "answer": "start"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "wear off",
                        "answer": "fade away"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "look after",
                        "answer": "take care of"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "show off",
                        "answer": "display proudly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "dress up",
                        "answer": "put on special clothes"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "cut in",
                        "answer": "interrupt"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "chip in",
                        "answer": "help"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "cheer up",
                        "answer": "become happier"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "come across",
                        "answer": "find unexpectedly"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "try out",
                        "answer": "test"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Verbs: Phrasal verbs"
        },
        {
            "quizPhrasalVerbsII": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizPhrasalVerbsII",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verbs: Phrasal verbs II",
                    "inputText": "Choose the correct phrasal verb",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Tom took Becky's candle and ... it ....",
                        "answer": "blew out"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Just as he was going to lie down, the eldest of the princesses brought him a cup of wine; but the soldier ... it all ... secretly, taking care not to drink a drop.",
                        "answer": "threw away"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"He does not ... ... us. Can he be a turkey?—We will see. If he does not like the water, he is not a duck.\"",
                        "answer": "look like"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "His granddad ... ... last night after a long illness.",
                        "answer": "passed away"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The little tailor began his game again, ... ... the biggest stone, and threw it with all his might on the breast of the first giant.",
                        "answer": "picked out"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They ... ... at the gym two times a week.",
                        "answer": "work out"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jake ... ... a story about why we were late.",
                        "answer": "made up"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I just ... ... the flu and now my whole family has it.",
                        "answer": "got over"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I thought that she would ... ... marrying till next year.",
                        "answer": "put off"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Brad ... ... the wedding because he wasn't in love with his fiancé.",
                        "answer": "called off"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Hey ... ... a minute.  I'll make you a snack to eat.  You might want it.\"",
                        "answer": "hold on"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I ... ... these old books when I was tidying the attic.",
                        "answer": "came across"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Do ... ... please. I will not disturb you\"",
                        "answer": "carry on"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Where can I ... ... the lights?\"",
                        "answer": "turn on"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The pain slowly ... ...",
                        "answer": "wore off"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Let me go out today, and you ... ... the house by yourself.' 'Yes, yes,' answered the mouse, 'by all means go, and if you get anything very good to eat, think of me.",
                        "answer": "look after"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He wanted to ... ... his new sound system.",
                        "answer": "show off"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I won't do it. You will all laugh at me. I won't ... ... like a girl.\"",
                        "answer": "dress up"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A lorry ... ... and nearly caused an accident.",
                        "answer": "cut in"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Everybody ... ... to pay for the trip.",
                        "answer": "chipped in"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Come on, ... ...; it isn't so bad, you know.",
                        "answer": "cheer up"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Rikki-tikki's mother (she used to live in the general's house at Segowlee) had carefully told Rikki what to do if ever he ... ... white men.",
                        "answer": "came across"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I ... ... the sweater before I bought it.",
                        "answer": "tried out"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Verbs: Phrasal verbs II"
        },
        {
            "verbParticiple": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "verbParticiple",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verbs: ( førnutid/førdatid udvidet )",
                    "inputText": "Insert the right verb.",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "\"I've heard what you fellows ... ... .... But don't be afraid. I'm not coming over.\"",
                        "answer": "have been saying"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She ... ... ... to behave herself with dignity; but now she burst into a violent fit of laughter, threw herself backwards over the chair, and rolled around on the floor.",
                        "answer": "had been trying"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Why, what ... you ... ... with your eyes, child?\" asked the old lady. \"Crying,\" answered the princess.",
                        "answer": "have been doing"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "It was a hard down-hill road, and she ... ... ... very fast—so it was no wonder she began to cry.",
                        "answer": "had been running"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "It ... ... ... heavily for one whole month.",
                        "answer": "had been raining"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"My precious darling princess! where have you been? What has happened to you? We ... all ... ... our eyes out, and searching the house from top to bottom for you.\"",
                        "answer": "have been crying"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"What can that noise be?\" said one of the housemaids, who ... ... ... for a moment or two.",
                        "answer": "had been listening"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Tonight, when the robbers are all asleep, we will flee together. I ... long ... ... for an opportunity to escape.'",
                        "answer": "have been waiting"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Then the first looked round and said, 'Who ... ... ... on my bed?'",
                        "answer": "has been lying"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'Who ... ... ... out of my little glass?'",
                        "answer": "has been drinking"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Hansel, however, ... not ... ... back at the cat, but had been constantly throwing one of the white pebble-stones out of his pocket on the road.",
                        "answer": "had been looking"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Verbs: Present/Past perfect continuous ( førnutid/førdatid udvidet )"
        },
        {
            "quizDorkDiaries": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizDorkDiaries",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary",
                    "subTitle": "School - Dork Diaries",
                    "inputText": "Choose the right word",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "I was trying to remain calm and not ... ... too much.”",
                        "answer": "freak out"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We’ve also seen hunters shoot mother bears dead, leaving behind orphaned cubs, who are unlikely to ... alone.",
                        "answer": "survive"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Dork Diaries"
        },
        {
            "quizNounsPlural": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizNounsPlural",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Plural nouns",
                    "inputText": "Write the plural form of the singular noun",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "cherry",
                        "answer": "cherries"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "city",
                        "answer": "cities"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "baby",
                        "answer": "babies"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "country",
                        "answer": "countries"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "church",
                        "answer": "churches"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "box",
                        "answer": "boxes"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "bus",
                        "answer": "buses"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "hero",
                        "answer": "heroes"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "woman",
                        "answer": "women"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "child",
                        "answer": "children"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "goose",
                        "answer": "geese"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "tooth",
                        "answer": "teeth"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "sheep",
                        "answer": "sheep"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "man",
                        "answer": "men"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "mouse",
                        "answer": "mice"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "half",
                        "answer": "halves"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "knife",
                        "answer": "knives"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "life",
                        "answer": "lives"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "radio",
                        "answer": "radios"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "pants",
                        "answer": "pants"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "shorts",
                        "answer": "shorts"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "book",
                        "answer": "books"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "From singular to plural"
        },
        {
            "adjectivesComparison": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "adjectivesComparison",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Adjectives (degrees)",
                    "inputText": "Choose the right adjective",
                    "showAnswers": "True"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "The nearer it got to noon that day the ... was the wagons and horses in the streets, and more coming all the time.",
                        "answer": "thicker"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A large hedge of thorns soon grew round the palace, and every year it became ... and thicker; till at last the old palace was surrounded and hidden, so that not even the roof or the chimneys could be seen.",
                        "answer": "higher"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "His fur was much ... than Bagheera's, but he had suffered sorely in the fight.",
                        "answer": "thicker"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The road led him up a mountain, and when he had reached the ... point of it, there sat a powerful giant looking peacefully about him.",
                        "answer": "highest"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A shepherd's dog had a master who took no care of him, but often let him suffer the ... hunger.",
                        "answer": "greatest"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"There are no ... words than what might have been.\"",
                        "answer": "sadder"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Because of the accident, it was one of the ... days of my life.",
                        "answer": "saddest"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'This is no good,' said he: 'try and spin; perhaps you will do that ....' So she sat down and tried to spin; but the threads cut her tender fingers till the blood ran.",
                        "answer": "better"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"No. Who's Robin Hood?\"  \"Why, he was one of the greatest men that was ever in England—and the ....",
                        "answer": "best"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Then Brok took out the golden pig. He said, \"This pig can go anywhere, on the ground or in the air. It can go ... than any horse. If the night is dark, the shining pig will make it light.\"",
                        "answer": "faster"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Oh!\" cried the nurse with a sigh that was almost a scream, and ran on ... than ever.",
                        "answer": "faster"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Right then a thought came to him. It gave him just a little bit of hope, and seemed to help him run just a little ....",
                        "answer": "faster"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Having examined it, she opened the casket, and took from it a little ointment. The ... odor filled the room—like that of roses and lilies—as she rubbed the ointment gently all over the hot swollen hand.",
                        "answer": "sweetest"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "And still the path grew rougher and steeper, and the mountain grew ..., till Irene began to think she was going a very long way from home.",
                        "answer": "wilder"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Not in my ... dreams did I think I would be here five years ago,\" she said.",
                        "answer": "wildest"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Adjectives ( degrees )"
        },
        {
            "quizVerbsIrregularFørNutid_I": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizVerbsIrregularFørNutid_I",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verbs: Irregular (Førnutid/Førdatid)",
                    "inputText": "Insert the right form of the verb in the parenthesis",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "\"He is buried beside mother in the churchyard yonder. Now that you are here I thank God that he didn't live to see what you ... ....\"(become)",
                        "answer": "have become"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "“I ... ... to bring you home, dear brother!” said the child, clapping her tiny hands, and bending down to laugh. “To bring you home, home, home!”(come)",
                        "answer": "have come"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Ever since he ... ... Shadow in the trap which he had set for him in the henhouse, Farmer Brown's boy had been puzzling over what he should do with his prisoner.(find)",
                        "answer": "had found"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'What ... you ... in your apron?'(get)",
                        "answer": "have got"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "At last, when they ... all but ... it up, just as the sun rose, the prince opened his eyes. (give)",
                        "answer": "had given"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Meanwhile he ... ... outside again and mounted his horse and thrown off the cloak.(go)",
                        "answer": "had gone"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I also ... ... what love is.\"(know)",
                        "answer": "have known"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They ... ... the fire burning, and the light came through brighter than before.(leave)",
                        "answer": "had left"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"You can all go to bed right away,\" he said when he ... ... his preparations.(make)",
                        "answer": "had made"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "And scarcely ... the wolf ... this, than with one bound he was out of bed and swallowed up Red-Cap.(say)",
                        "answer": "had said"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "For though he had been so great a traveller, and ... done and ... so many fine things, and was fond enough of telling the whole story, he always agreed that, after all, there's no place like HOME!(see)",
                        "answer": "had seen"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He ... ... up late for class yesterday.(show)",
                        "answer": "had shown"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She had been born while he was in prison, but it ... not ... any time at all for him to learn to love her.(take)",
                        "answer": "had taken"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"Huck, ... you ever ... anybody about—that?\"(tell)",
                        "answer": "have told"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"I ... just ... of a splendid joke. I shall pour my medicine into Nana's bowl, and she will drink it, thinking it is milk!\"(think)",
                        "answer": "have thought"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Verbs: Irregular ( Førnutid/Førdatid ) I"
        },
        {
            "quizVerbsIrregularFørNutid_II": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "quizVerbsIrregularFørNutid_II",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Verbs: Irregular (Førnutid/Førdatid) II",
                    "inputText": "Insert the right form of the verb in the parenthesis",
                    "showAnswers": "False"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "\"They ... ... to fight!\" I cried. \"look!\"(begin)",
                        "answer": "have begun"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "'Open the door for me, children, your dear little mother has come home, and ... ... every one of you something back from the forest with her.'(bring)",
                        "answer": "has brought"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "For she ... ... all the time that Curdie was not believing what she had told him.(feel)",
                        "answer": "had felt"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "But the huntsman ... ... all they said; and as soon as they were gone, he climbed to the top of the mountain.(hear)",
                        "answer": "had heard"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"... I ... you waiting?\"(keep)",
                        "answer": "Have kept"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He ... said he ... to enlist, and from the humour that he was in when he went away we guessed it to be in some regiment where he could get to the wars.(mean)",
                        "answer": "had meant"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "On this particular day it was nearly three months since they ... ....(meet)",
                        "answer": "had met"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Now I ... finally ... for my sins.(pay)",
                        "answer": "have paid"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "When she saw the flowers she knew at once who ... ... them there.(put)",
                        "answer": "had put"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "\"We must ... ... into Africa,\" said the Doctor. \"Dear me, dear me!—Well—we must all swim to land.\"(run)",
                        "answer": "have run"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The sun ... ... and the stars are shining; stars that are as bright and beautiful as your eyes.(set)",
                        "answer": "has set"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Diana ... ... up very unsteadily; then she sat down again, putting her hands to her head.(stand)",
                        "answer": "had stood"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "She said she ... never ... a letter and she didn't know how to, or what to say.(write)(write)",
                        "answer": "had written"
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Verbs: Irregular (Førnutid/Førdatid) II"
        }
    ],
    "scrambled": [
        {
            "halloween": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "halloween",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Halloween",
                    "selectWords": "a I",
                    "quote": "Online activities, the mp3 and printable handouts are available for this lesson at http://www.eslholidaylessons.com"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "Halloween is celebrated on October the 31st."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "It originated from a pagan holiday and the Christian holiday of All-Saints’ Day."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Halloween is probably most famous in the U.S.A"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Some Christians are not so happy about Halloween."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Halloween has many easily identifiable symbols."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The colours orange and black are widely used."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "One of the biggest Halloween activities is trick-or-treating."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Children knock on doors and ask for a small gift."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Food also plays a big part of Halloween."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Toffee apples are very popular and so is anything made from pumpkin."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Halloween is also a popular topic for Hollywood."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "scrambleJackLantern": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "scrambleJackLantern",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Halloween - Jack O'Lantern",
                    "lowerCaseCharacters": "true",
                    "quote": "by Page McKean Zyromski, An AmericanCatholic.org Web Site from the Franciscans and Franciscan Media",
                    "selectWords": "a I cried"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "according to legend, Jack grew up in a village in Ireland."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "he earned a reputation for cleverness as well as laziness."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Jack first met the Devil at the local pub."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "he challenged the Devil but he only snorted at such child’s play."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "instantly, the Devil turned himself into a coin."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Jack held the coin in his hand which had a cross-shaped scar."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Jack figured he could repent later."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "the agreed-upon day arrived and death took him by surprise."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "St. Peter shook his head and could not let him in."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "\"Where can I go?\" cried Jack. \"How can I see in the darkness?\""
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "scrambledPuritans": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "scrambledPuritans",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Native americans - Puritans"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "They called themselves \"the godly\", but other people called them \"Puritans.\""
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Mainly these people wanted to live quiet, simple lives."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "They spend a lot of time praying and reading the Bible."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Puritans wore plain clothes and lived in plain houses."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "They often went to church."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "They believed that God wanted them to work very hard."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The Puritans got into trouble with other people."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "In 1630 AD, Puritans came to Massachusetts to start a colony."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "These Puritans were mostly richer and more educated than others in America."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "scrambledHawaiiFacts": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "scrambledHawaiiFacts",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Hawaii - Interesting Facts",
                    "lowerCaseCharacters": "true",
                    "selectWords": "ethnically west capitol and east thousands diverse both"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "hawaii is the only state that grows coffee."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "one-third of the world's commercial supply of pineapples comes from Hawaii."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "there are only 12 letters in the Hawaiian alphabet."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Hawaii is the widest state in the United States."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "volcanoes that erupted thousands of years ago formed the islands of Hawaii."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Hawaii was the 50th state admitted to the union on August 20th, 1959."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "it is the most ethnically and racially diverse state in the union."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "honolulu, the capitol and largest city, is located on the island of Oahu."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "aloha is used both as “hello” and “goodbye."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "due to volcanic activity, Hawaii is the only state that is still growing."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "adjectivesOrder": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "adjectivesOrder",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Adjectives (order)",
                    "lowerCaseCharacters": "false",
                    "selectWords": "bought threw always have a",
                    "dontBindWords": "true"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "I bought a pair of black leather shoes."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "I threw away my dirty, old sofa."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "It is a quiet, old town."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "I always bring my small, red sleeping bag."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "On the table sits a huge, round metal bowl."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The dolfin is a beautiful, intelligent animal."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "What a handsome, young man you have become."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "I have found an expensive, antique, silver mirror at the flea market."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Please order that delicious Vietnamese food we had last week."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The neighbour has a big, black dog."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "scramblesBearAttacks": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "scramblesBearAttacks",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Wilderness - Surviving bear attacks",
                    "lowerCaseCharacters": "false",
                    "selectWords": "a"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "Bears seldomly attack people in the woods."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Bear attacks are extremely rare."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "If it does happen, what would you do?"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Running away is a bad thing to do, and it might think that you are a prey."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "It is also very unlikely that you are able to outrun a bear."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Choosing what to do depends on what kind of bear you meet."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Grizzly bears will propably not attack you if you 'play dead'."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "If you choose to lie down, you should also protect your neck."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "'Playing dead' is also a good idea if it is a female bear with cubs."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Male bears can climb trees and sometimes eat people."
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Wilderness - Surviving bear attacks II"
        },
        {
            "scrambledWildrenessShripwreck": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "scrambledWildrenessShripwreck",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Wilderness - Surviving shripwrecks",
                    "lowerCaseCharacters": "false",
                    "selectWords": "a"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "What would you bring with you if your ship went down?"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Maybe you would only have time to bring a few things."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Food is not as important as you might think."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "There is a good chance that you will be rescued within 72 hours."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "You need to bring something that can be seen by your rescuers."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Shiny things that refelct sunlight and bright colored clothes."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "You also need fresh water."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Warm clothing is needed if you are to survive in cold weather."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "People sometimes die of hypothemia in just a few hours."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Look for food when you have something to signal with, warm clothes and water."
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Wilderness - Surviving shripwrecks"
        }
    ],
    "sortable": [
        {
            "sortableJackLantern": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "sortableJackLantern",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Halloween - Jack O'Lantern II",
                    "quote": "by Page McKean Zyromski, An AmericanCatholic.org Web Site from the Franciscans and\nFranciscan Media"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "1. According to legend, Jack",
                        "answer": "grew up in a village in Ireland."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "2. He earned a reputation for",
                        "answer": "cleverness as well as laziness."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "3. Jack first met the Devil",
                        "answer": "at the local pub."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "4. He challenged the Devil but he only",
                        "answer": "snorted at such child’s play."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "5. Instantly, the devil turned",
                        "answer": "himself into a coin."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "6. Jack held the coin in his hand",
                        "answer": "which bore a cross-shaped scar."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "7. Jack figured he",
                        "answer": "could repent later."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "8. But the agreed-upon day arrived",
                        "answer": "and death took him by surprise."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "9. St. Peter shook his head and",
                        "answer": "could not let him in."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "10. Where can I go?\" cried Jack.",
                        "answer": "\"How can I see in the darkness?\""
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "sortableJaybird": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "sortableJaybird",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Native Americans - Jaybird"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "Native americans were already living",
                        "answer": "in America when Columbus arrived"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The members of the Pennacock",
                        "answer": "tribe did not kill the settlers"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The Puritans came from Europe in order",
                        "answer": "to live by their own principles"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Jaybird and Mary became",
                        "answer": "best friends"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The native americans helped",
                        "answer": "the european settlers when they arrived"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "When the white men came, disease became the",
                        "answer": "main cause of death in the Pennacock tribe"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Jaybird realised that",
                        "answer": "he could not go home"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The native americans",
                        "answer": "did not easily adopt the white man's culture"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The puritans took the Bible literally",
                        "answer": "and lived simple lives."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "In the winter, the native americans go deeper",
                        "answer": "into the forest and come back in the spring"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "sortableMaidenWarrior": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "sortableMaidenWarrior",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Native americans - The Maiden Warrior",
                    "inputText": "undefined",
                    "showAnswers": "undefined"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "1. The Mingoes and the Oneidas are at war",
                        "answer": "with each other."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "2. The Mingoes have destroyed",
                        "answer": "their villages."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "3. The Oneidas have",
                        "answer": "hidden in caves."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "4. A young girl called Aliquipiso",
                        "answer": "knows how to save her people."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "5. She is to lead the Mingoes",
                        "answer": "to the foot of the cliff."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "6. Mingo scouts found her",
                        "answer": "and brought her to the village."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "7. The Mingoes totured her and at last",
                        "answer": "she pretended to weaken under the pain."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "8. Silently the Mingoes crept behind",
                        "answer": "her through thickets and rough places."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "9. The Mingoes scarcely had time to",
                        "answer": "strike when rocks rained upon them."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "10. The story of the girl's courage and",
                        "answer": "self-sacrifice was retold around campfires."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "makingNationSort": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "makingNationSort",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Native americans - The making of a Nation",
                    "wordsOnly": "false",
                    "alignCenter": "false"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "1. The United States began to expand west during",
                        "answer": "the middle eighteen hundreds"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "2. Indians had lived in the western",
                        "answer": "territories for hundreds of years"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "3. Whenever white men wanted Indian land,",
                        "answer": "the tribes were pushed farther west"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "4. The Indians were given land",
                        "answer": "in what is now known as Oklahoma"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "5. The Indians of the western grasslands",
                        "answer": "refused to give up their way of life"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "6. The plains Indians were always on",
                        "answer": "the move, because they hunted buffalo"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "7. The plains Indians did not want",
                        "answer": "white men crossing their hunting lands"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "8. They tried to protect the wagon trains",
                        "answer": "from Indian attacks"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "9. The Santee Sioux signed treaties with the",
                        "answer": "government giving up ninety percent of their land"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "10. The Santee agreed to live in a small area,",
                        "answer": "and the United States agreed to give them food"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "makingNationSort2": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "makingNationSort2",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Native americans - The making of a Nation II",
                    "wordsOnly": "false",
                    "alignCenter": "false"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "1. The government was late giving the",
                        "answer": "Santee Indians their payment"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "2. The Santee Indians became hungry",
                        "answer": "and they decided to go to war"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "3. Lakota Sioux tribe fought bitterly to",
                        "answer": "keep white men out of their hunting grounds"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "4. The government decided to put aside an",
                        "answer": "area of land for each tribe called a 'reservation'"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "5. The Indians did not want to give up",
                        "answer": "their old ways of living"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "6. As the whites moved in, the buffalo",
                        "answer": "and other animals left"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "7. Soldiers shared their food with the",
                        "answer": "Indians but It was not enough"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "8. Indians were also given permission to hunt",
                        "answer": "buffalo in a wide area south of the reservations"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "9. As before, some of the Indians became",
                        "answer": "angry and refused to wait for food"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "10. In the end, they",
                        "answer": "failed to win back their land"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "sortableHawaiiFactsII": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "sortableHawaiiFactsII",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Hawaii - Interesting Facts II",
                    "wordsOnly": "false",
                    "alignCenter": "false"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "Hawaii is the newest",
                        "answer": "of the fifty states."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The world's largest active volcano, Kilouea, is on the",
                        "answer": "big island of Hawaii."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Surfing was invented in Hawaii and the",
                        "answer": "Banzai Pipeline is the most famous surfing place."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The only royal palace in the United States",
                        "answer": "is on the island of Oahu."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The island of Kauai has been used to make",
                        "answer": "many movies. Jurassic Park was made on Kauai."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Until 1921, Waikiki was a flat marshy",
                        "answer": "field used for growing taro plants."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The capitol of Hawaii",
                        "answer": "is called Honolulo"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Whale watching is a popular attraction on",
                        "answer": "the island of Maui."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "A luau is a big beach dinner where the main course",
                        "answer": "is a pig cooked on rocks in the ground."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "The hula is a dance done by both men",
                        "answer": "and women in Hawaii."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "sortableBearAttacks": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "sortableBearAttacks",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Wilderness - Surviving bear attacks II",
                    "wordsOnly": "false",
                    "alignCenter": "false"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "Bears seldomly attack",
                        "answer": "people in the woods."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Bear attacks are extremely",
                        "answer": "rare"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "If it does happen,",
                        "answer": "what would you do?"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Running away is a bad thing to do,",
                        "answer": "and it might think that you are a prey."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "It is also very unlikely that you are",
                        "answer": "able to outrun a bear."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Choosing what to do",
                        "answer": "depends on what kind of bear you meet."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Grizzly bears will propably",
                        "answer": "not attack you if you 'play dead'"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "If you choose to lie down,",
                        "answer": "you should also protect your neck."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "'Playing dead' is also a good idea",
                        "answer": "if it is a female bear with cubs."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Male bears can climb trees and they",
                        "answer": "sometimes eat people."
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Wilderness - Surviving bear attacks"
        },
        {
            "sortableWildernessShipwreck": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "sortableWildernessShipwreck",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Wilderness - Surviving shripwrecks II",
                    "wordsOnly": "false",
                    "alignCenter": "false"
                },
                "sentences": [
                    {
                        "sentence": "What would you bring with",
                        "answer": "you if your ship went down?"
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Maybe you would only have time",
                        "answer": "to bring a few things."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Food is not as important as",
                        "answer": "you might think."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "There is a good chance that",
                        "answer": "you will be rescued within 72 hours."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "You need to bring something that",
                        "answer": "can be seen by your rescuers."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Shiny things that refelct",
                        "answer": "sunlight and bright colored clothes."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "You also need",
                        "answer": "fresh water."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Warm clothing is needed if you are to survive",
                        "answer": "in cold weather."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "People sometimes die of hypothemia",
                        "answer": "in just a few hours."
                    },
                    {
                        "sentence": "Look for food when you have something to",
                        "answer": "signal with, warm clothes and water."
                    }
                ]
            },
            "title": "Wilderness - Surviving Shripwrecks II"
        }
    ],
    "trueFalse": [
        {
            "jayBirdTrueFalse": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "jayBirdTrueFalse",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Native Americans - Jaybird II"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "There were no native americans living in America when Columbus arrived.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The indians instantly killed the settlers.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The Puritans came from Europe.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jaybird and Mary became fierce enemies.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "When the white men came, disease became the main cause of death among the members of the Pennacock tribe.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jaybird realised that he could not go home.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The native americans easily adopted the white man's culture.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The puritans read the Bible literally and lived simple lives.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The native americans helped the european settlers when they arrived.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "In the winter, the native americans go deeper into the forest and come back in the spring.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "jackLanternTrueFalse": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "jackLanternTrueFalse",
                    "headline": "Theme",
                    "subTitle": "Halloween - Jack O'Lantern III"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Jack really cared about other people.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jack was very dumb.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Gambling was a pastime at which he excelled.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "In his life he made many enemies.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "One Halloween the time came for Jack to die.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "When the devil arrived to take his soul, Jack was lazily drinking at the pub.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He asked the Devil permission to finish his ale.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jack decided to see if the Devil would be willing to transform himself into a shilling.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The devil instantly changed himself into a shilling.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Everyone knows the devil is powerless when faced with the cross.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jack would not let the devil free until he gave him another ale.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The devil left Jack at the pub.",
                        "answer": "true"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Satan could easily resist a game of dice.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "St. Peter was glad to see him on the day of his death.",
                        "answer": "false"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The devil tossed a burning coal into a hollow pumpkin,",
                        "answer": "true"
                    }
                ]
            }
        }
    ],
    "doubleTrouble": [
        {
            "subjectsNVerbs": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "subjectsNVerbs",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "showAnswers": "False",
                    "subTitle": "Verbs and Subjects: (Find)",
                    "inputText": "Choose the first verb and simple or compound subject",
                    "secondAnswers": "true"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Do you like this music?",
                        "answer": "Do",
                        "secondAnswer": "you"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I never thought about that.",
                        "answer": "thought",
                        "secondAnswer": "I"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "This is where I get off.",
                        "answer": "is",
                        "secondAnswer": "This"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I am waiting for a phone call",
                        "answer": "am",
                        "secondAnswer": "I"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I was reading a book",
                        "answer": "was",
                        "secondAnswer": "I"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He is too slow.",
                        "answer": "is",
                        "secondAnswer": "He"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "What is the password?",
                        "answer": "is",
                        "secondAnswer": "password"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Can you help me solve this?",
                        "answer": "Can",
                        "secondAnswer": "you"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Where are you going?",
                        "answer": "are",
                        "secondAnswer": "you"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "My parents are visiting me",
                        "answer": "are",
                        "secondAnswer": "parents"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "We arrived at 2 o'clock",
                        "answer": "arrived",
                        "secondAnswer": "We"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "I never got to say goodbye",
                        "answer": "got",
                        "secondAnswer": "I"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "At what time will we get there?",
                        "answer": "will",
                        "secondAnswer": "we"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They shook his hand on arrival.",
                        "answer": "shook",
                        "secondAnswer": "They"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Neither of them had any clue as to what was going on.",
                        "answer": "had",
                        "secondAnswer": "Neither"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jake and I went on a camping trip last summer.",
                        "answer": "went",
                        "secondAnswer": "Jake and I"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jake and his dad took charge of finding and preparing a campground.",
                        "answer": "took",
                        "secondAnswer": "Jake and his dad"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A wooden feeder for the birds hangs outside my window.",
                        "answer": "hangs",
                        "secondAnswer": "feeder"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The clear, soft whistles of the goldfinches often echo in the woods nearby.",
                        "answer": "echo",
                        "secondAnswer": "whistles"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "A black shadow dropped down into the circle.",
                        "answer": "dropped",
                        "secondAnswer": "shadow"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Both my boots and socks were soaking wet.",
                        "answer": "were",
                        "secondAnswer": "boots and socks"
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "adjectivesFind": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "adjectivesFind",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "showAnswers": "False",
                    "subTitle": "Adjectives: (Find)",
                    "inputText": "Choose the adjective and the word it describes",
                    "secondAnswers": "true"
                },
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "She is fairly intelligent.",
                        "answer": "intelligent",
                        "secondAnswer": "She"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "This is a large house.",
                        "answer": "large",
                        "secondAnswer": "house"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Get me off this godforsaken island.",
                        "answer": "godforsaken",
                        "secondAnswer": "island"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "This is the worst book I have ever read.",
                        "answer": "worst",
                        "secondAnswer": "book"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Eating candy is my favorite pastime.",
                        "answer": "favorite",
                        "secondAnswer": "pastime"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "He is too slow.",
                        "answer": "slow",
                        "secondAnswer": "He"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "This is the biggest house I have ever seen.",
                        "answer": "biggest",
                        "secondAnswer": "house"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "This is my last warning.",
                        "answer": "last",
                        "secondAnswer": "warning"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Jack is taller than Jim.",
                        "answer": "taller",
                        "secondAnswer": "Jack"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "They are very much alike.",
                        "answer": "alike",
                        "secondAnswer": "They"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The homeless in London sleep under bridges.",
                        "answer": "homeless",
                        "secondAnswer": "None of the words"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The blind man refused to answer.",
                        "answer": "blind",
                        "secondAnswer": "man"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "The drunken sailor smiled at her.",
                        "answer": "drunken",
                        "secondAnswer": "sailor"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Everybody was annoyed.",
                        "answer": "annoyed",
                        "secondAnswer": "Everybody"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Give me that old time religion.",
                        "answer": "old",
                        "secondAnswer": "time"
                    }
                ]
            }
        }
    ],
    "gapFill": [
        {
            "gapFillCanyon": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "gapFillCanyon",
                    "headline": "Theme/Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Native americans, Prepositions - Glen Canyon Dam",
                    "inputText": "Insert the prepositions",
                    "quote": "Inspired by Gap-Fill Exercise by Barbara Dieu"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "aliceChapter2a": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "aliceChapter2a",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary/Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland( Lewis Carroll ), Nouns - Chapter 2, The Pool of Tears(a).",
                    "inputText": "Insert the nouns",
                    "quote": "Source: Project Gutenberg"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "aliceChapter2b": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "aliceChapter2b",
                    "headline": "Vocabulary/Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland( Lewis Carroll ), Verbs - Chapter 2, The Pool of Tears(b).",
                    "inputText": "Insert the verbs",
                    "quote": "Source: Project Gutenberg"
                }
            }
        }
    ],
    "transition": [
        {
            "rumplestiltskin": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "rumplestiltskin",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Cohesion and coherence - Grimm's fairytales: Rumplestiltskin.",
                    "textFile": "rumplestiltskin",
                    "quoteText": "Source: Project Gutenberg"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "realPrincess": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "realPrincess",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Cohesion and coherence - H.C.Andersen: The Real Princess.",
                    "textFile": "realPrincess",
                    "quoteText": "Source: Project Gutenberg"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "theCyclone": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "theCyclone",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Cohesion and coherence - L. Frank Baum: The Wonderful Wizard of Oz. Chapter 1, The Cyclone.",
                    "textFile": "theCyclone",
                    "quoteText": "Source: Project Gutenberg",
                    "mustBeBound": "and rarely spoke,the grass coming from that direction also,Aunt Em dropped,Then a strange thing,Toto did not like it"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "happyJack": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "happyJack",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Cohesion and coherence - Thornton W. Burgess: Happy Jack. Chapter 1, Happy Jack drops a nut.",
                    "textFile": "happyJack",
                    "quoteText": "Source: Project Gutenberg",
                    "mustBeBound": ""
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "aliceWonderland": {
                "info": {
                    "title": "aliceWonderland",
                    "headline": "Grammar",
                    "subTitle": "Cohesion and coherence - Lewis Carroll: Alice's Adventures in Wonderland. Chapter 1, Down the rabbit hole.",
                    "textFile": "aliceWonderland",
                    "quoteText": "Source: Project Gutenberg",
                    "mustBeBound": ""
                }
            }
        }
    ],
    "jumbled": {
        "jumbledFruit": {
            "info": {
                "title": "jumbledFruit",
                "headline": "Grammar",
                "subTitle": "Fruit"
            },
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Large sweet tropical fruit.",
                    "answer": "Pineapple"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Fruit with red or yellow or green skin.",
                    "answer": "Apple"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Citrus fruit.",
                    "answer": "Orange"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Green or purple fruits that grow on a vine.",
                    "answer": "Grape"
                },
                {
                    "question": "A long tropical fruit.",
                    "answer": "Banana"
                },
                {
                    "question": "A red fruit with a hard stone.",
                    "answer": "Cherry"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sweet juicy fruit.",
                    "answer": "Pear"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Yellow juicy sweet fruit.",
                    "answer": "Peach"
                },
                {
                    "question": "A large round fruit.",
                    "answer": "Watermelon"
                },
                {
                    "question": "A soft red juicy fruit.",
                    "answer": "Strawberry"
                }
            ]
        }
    }
}